Now let's talk about the new features and functional optimization of the 7.3 pudding version, mainly explained in four aspects, the main functions, 2D, materials and rendering.
Let's first introduce the main functions. The first main function is the AI sticker generator.
When creating a sticker, there is no need to edit it. For example, by entering key words to delete the background.
You can also try to look at the created sticker pattern on 3D clothing to ensure that the sticker pattern matches the 3D clothing.
Currently, the AI sticker generator can easily create stickers with embroidery, design and wave art characteristics.
The current AI sticker generator is a public version of the function. Future use policies may change.
Next, let's take a look at how to open the AI sticker generator.
There are two ways here, corresponding to different application scenarios.
First, let's look at the first way. If you want to create a new sticker pattern, you can click on the sticker in the object window.
Then click on the magic bar icon above, which is the AI sticker generator.
The second way is.
If you want to use the AI sticker generator on the sticker that has already been added, you can select the desired sticker.
Then click on the attribute editor, the AI sticker generator next to the default parameters.
Next, let's take a look at the interface of the AI sticker generator.
First, let's look at the first option, the pattern type.
In the pattern type, we can create a sticker pattern that is closer to what we want.
After the pattern type selects the art style, you can select the style to be reflected in the sticker from the drop-down menu.
Currently, there are three styles of embroidery, fashion, wave art.
If you want to create one that is not affected by any pattern type, and only creates AI stickers through hints, the pattern type can be selected as 5.
If you want to create a sticker with a transparent background, you need to select the option of a transparent background.
Next is the key word prompt.
In the key word prompt box, enter the key word of the pattern you want to create.
The AI sticker will be previewed at the bottom after creation.
If you click on the history record option on the right, it will display the history of the creation.
In addition, you can also check the options and key words selected when creating the sticker.
Note that the history record will only be retained until the cloud software is closed.
Therefore, the history record will only be retained until the cloud software is closed.
Next, let's take a look at the function use process.
The pattern type is no exception.
Next, we will create an AI sticker by entering the key word.
In the key word prompt box, enter the key word that describes the image you want to create.
Here is a tip.
Here are the tips for entering the key words.
First, in terms of language, the AI sticker generator supports languages ​​in more than 50 countries.
We can use any language provided by cloud.
Here, it is recommended that you enter the key word in English, because the English prompt is relatively accurate.
In addition, when entering the key word, it is recommended to enter a word instead of a long descriptive sentence.
A long sentence may cause the image to be distorted.
When entering the key word, please use the dot or the space bar to separate.
Here we enter the key word.
If you want to emphasize the characteristics of certain key words, you can use the space bar.
After using the space bar, the number of key words will increase.
After entering the question, click on the Create button to create a sticker.
When creating an AI sticker, you can see the current server link and the progress of the creation.
When creating a picture, if there are more users in line, you may need to wait for a longer time to complete it.
In this case, you can use the arrow button in the upper right corner of the unit to minimize the window.
Once the sticker is created, there will be a text prompt display to make it useful.
After completing the creation of the AI sticker image, click on the App button.
The created image will be added to the object window.
This will make the new image an application for the sticker.
If you want to check the effect of the existing sticker on the costume, you need to select it in the object window first.
Then drag it to the desired position of the 3D costume.
You can easily check if it is suitable for the costume.
Next, we will use embroidery as an example.
We select the art style in the pattern type.
Select the embroidery in the drop-down window.
Select the transparent background.
Create an embroidery sticker with a transparent background.
Enter the keyword.
Then click on the Create button.
You can apply the created sticker to the 3D costume immediately by clicking on the application.
You can see the effect of the sticker.
In order to generate as many new diversified images as possible,
even with the same prompt, the AI sticker generator will generate different results every time.
If you want to update the prompt at the same time,
you can keep the previous generated result characteristics as possible.
You can click on the true icon.
The mouse will be suspended on the true icon.
It will display the prompt of the tool.
Keep the prompt result to generate similar results.
Just as the description in the tool prompt.
Click on the fixed icon.
It will generate a new image that is similar to the previous generated image.
Remember that the generated image result may be different.
It depends on whether the prompt is added or modified.
If you need to add a new image,
you can click on the random button.
The pattern type and keywords are randomly selected and entered.
Using the AI sticker generator, you can easily create the stickers you want.
Now let's introduce the second main function,
the virtual model face generator.
This function is developed in cooperation with NOVA.
Its main feature is that it can change the existing close-up image.
This feature is very useful.
It can change the face of the existing close-up virtual model.
It not only changes the texture of the virtual model,
but also uses AI-generated facial images
or uploads specific facial image files
to change the virtual model's facial grid structure.
The virtual model after conversion is the unique virtual model format of close-up.
It can be used immediately.
It can also be applied to the virtual model of various virtual models
provided by the TuKu window and the Connect platform.
For the facial image generation based on AI,
users can select the required gender, age range and race as the preset,
and input the key words of the relevant characteristics to generate it.
Another way is to directly upload the facial image you want to generate.
All you need to do is to select the image upload collection that meets the requirements.
Now let's take a look at the functional use process.
First, let's run the virtual model.
We have two ways to run this function.
The first is to use the virtual model human generator
under the virtual model menu in the top main menu bar.
The second is to press the virtual model,
and then use the virtual model human generator tool
in the body model box in the attribute editor
to visit it.
First, let's take a look at the window interface of the virtual model human generator.
At the top of the window,
you can choose between the prompt option and the picture option.
The prompt option allows you to create and convert images based on AI,
and the picture option allows you to upload specific image files to the face.
Let's use the prompt option first.
In the top menu bar,
you can select the required face gender, age group and race.
The gender option will be selected based on the gender of the virtual model you choose,
and it will automatically set the gender of the virtual model you choose.
Currently, this function is only applicable to female virtual models,
but the range of selected gender will gradually increase in the future version.
The age option allows you to use the preset setting
for the age of the face you want to create.
Currently, you can choose the age range from 10 to 80 years old for the preset.
Through the race option,
you can use the preset setting for the race of the face you want to create.
The preset options currently available are
Asian,
Caucasian,
African,
Middle Eastern,
and Latin American.
In the key word prompt window,
enter the keyword that describes the required face gender.
In the bottom AI face gender section,
you can check the face gender images based on AI generation.
If you want to re-visit the image of the virtual model,
similar to the physical generation period,
click on the historical record option on the right.
The window will open,
allowing you to check the face image of the virtual model,
and the options and hints set for creating these images.
Please note that the historical record of the record
is only reserved until the Clore software is closed.
Next, let's take a look at the image options.
Through the top image menu,
you can select the gender of the virtual model to be converted.
The gender option will be set according to the gender of the virtual model.
Click on the upload button in the picture window.
To upload the image,
you need to use the specific image file for the face conversion.
If you want to re-visit the image of the upload,
please click on the historical record option on the right.
The window will open,
and you can check the face image of the upload.
Similar to the prompt option,
the historical record of the record
is reserved until the Clore software is closed.
Next, let's do the operation.
Set the option,
enter the key word prompt and generate.
Now let's create a human face image based on AI technology.
First, in the options,
select the age and race of the face you want to create.
In the text prompt section,
enter the text that describes the features of the face.
This function supports about 50 languages.
All languages provided by Clore can be used.
However, due to the high accuracy of the input English prompt,
it is recommended to write the prompt in English.
After entering the prompt,
you must click on the start button to create the image.
Next,
in order to improve the quality of the generated virtual model face,
please refer to the reference image shown in the AI human face checkbox.
It is recommended to check before switching
whether the created image has responded well to the following points.
The face special image
and the image that the face is not covered by hair or shadows
After fully understanding these suggestions,
click on the start button to create the image.
When creating the image,
you can check the progress of the server connection
and the number of rows.
After creating the image of the face,
click on the switch button.
You will see the face of the Clore virtual model
change according to the image of the face created.
In this process,
the body texture and color of the virtual model
will also change,
maintaining the natural coordination with the face color of the created image.
After setting the gender of the face to be created,
age and race selection,
if you need ideas or help with facial features,
please click on the random icon in the brush shape.
At this time,
a hint that describes the human face will be entered randomly.
Even if you use the same hint keyword,
the results generated by the AI human face will not be the same.
If you want to create different facial images
or update the hint while maintaining the original result,
please click on the true icon.
When you select the mouse on the true icon,
a tool will appear.
It points out that the key words to be kept in the input
have generated similar results.
As explained by the tool hint,
by clicking on the true icon,
you can create a new image
with a similar feeling to the image created before.
Let's click on the true button,
update the hint, and then generate.
Create a new image while maintaining the original result.
When modifying the hint,
please note that the new result may be
due to the addition or modification of the hint.
When generating the human face and the image,
if there are more users at the same time,
the creation time may be longer.
In this waiting time,
you can perform other tasks while using this function.
If the waiting time is longer,
please click on the arrow button in the upper right corner
to minimize the window.
After the creation is completed,
it will display the progress hint to be used effectively.
Finally, I will share some tips for inputting hint keywords
to create the facial image you want.
When typing a word,
it is recommended to type the word you need
rather than the long descriptive sentence.
This can produce more effective results.
In order to prevent the image from being lost due to the long sentence,
it is best to use two numbers to divide the word.
If you want to emphasize a specific word,
please use the square number around the word you want to emphasize.
This gives the word more weight,
making it more influential.
Next, we will try to convert the face of the virtual model
to the face of the virtual model
by uploading a specific image to the face of the virtual model.
First, check if the gender of the virtual model you need
is reflected in the gender option.
Click on the upload button
to use a specific image file for the face you need.
In order to generate a high-quality virtual model face,
it is recommended to refer to the image displayed in the image viewfinder as a reference.
In addition,
it is recommended to use the following image
to ensure that the image to be uploaded
is well reflected in the image viewfinder.
The image of the facial features
and the image of the face that has not been covered by hair or shadows.
After uploading the image file,
click on convert.
You will see the face of the virtual model
changed according to the uploaded image.
In this process,
the body texture and color of the virtual model will also change,
maintaining a natural coordination with the face tone of the window.
Before that,
you must have spent a lot of effort
to use virtual models that are realistic and diversified.
Now,
through the virtual face generator,
you can easily and quickly create virtual models that look like real life.
The AI face generator is currently a public version of the function.
In the future,
the policy and other aspects of its use may change.
The following are the functions of the 2D floating version.
First of all,
we are going to talk about the 2D CAD optimization of continuous editing.
The improvement of continuous editing
can improve the efficiency of work.
Next,
let's take a look at where the function is optimized.
In the previous version,
it is necessary to check whether the panels are already linked.
You need to use the editing panel tool
to focus on the single-frame section to be able to check.
From the floating version,
you can use the display link in the menu bar
on the upper left side of the window of the 2D panel
to display or hide the linked line diagram
to check whether the multiple lines are linked.
In addition,
before the floating version,
we need to right-click to set the linked line,
then select the editing link tool to remove the link.
For the floating line,
you need to select the edit floating line,
then right-click on the linked line to remove the link.
From this version,
in order to work more happily,
after selecting the edit panel tool,
you can also select the linked line
and right-click to remove the link.
In addition,
there are two more functions.
First,
we will talk about them together.
In the previous version,
after setting the linked line,
if the length or length of the linked line with the linked line is adjusted,
the linked state will remain,
but the length of the linked line will not be changed
to match the size of the edited line.
So from this version,
it has been improved.
After setting the linked line,
adjust the length of the line
or the proportion of the entire panel,
the linked line will also change in the same way.
Next,
we will show you
how to operate these improvement functions
in this version.
First,
use the edit panel tool
to select the linked line panel,
then adjust its size.
You can see that the linked line will be modified together.
When using the edit point or line tool
to move or rotate the line,
the length of the linked line remains unchanged,
and the length of the other lines will change.
Similarly,
use the edit panel tool
to select and drag the linked line
or the points on the line.
When using the edit panel tool,
press the right mouse button
and enter the value of the distance
in the output window.
The linked line will maintain its size value
and change.
When pressing the points on the line
and using the arrow on the keyboard
to adjust the line size,
use the same.
Finally,
if you select the two ends of the linked line at a time
and press the right mouse button,
use the array tool
to modify the position of the end point.
The array will be used in the same way
for the two ends of the linked line.
Using the linked edit function after optimization
can better improve the efficiency of work.
The next function to be introduced is
to improve the efficiency of selecting 2D panels.
After the function is improved,
you can press the shortcut button
and select the lines or panels you need.
To check this function,
open the project file with multiple inner lines.
Previously,
when the number of inner lines and shapes was too many,
as shown here,
you need to select some inner lines first,
and then cancel the unnecessary parts.
Now you can easily select the parts you want.
If you just want to select some folds in the skirt,
first select the edit panel tool in the 2D tool bar.
While pressing the CTRL key,
press the left mouse button,
you can select the inner lines you want to select.
Then you can see
all the lines that are selected
in the drag area are selected.
In addition to the inner lines,
you can also select the entire panel
by selecting only a part of the panel.
After selecting the edit panel tool,
press the CTRL key,
press the left mouse button to drag,
and select only a part of the panel you need.
You can see
all the panels in the drag area
will be selected.
You can easily select the inner lines and panels
you want to select by pressing the CTRL key.
The next feature I would like to introduce is
the 2D edit panel measurement angle.
We have developed a new feature
to check the angle of the panel's outline
or the angle of the line overlap.
The feature I would like to introduce this time
can check the angle of a specific position
when creating or modifying panels.
Let's look at this project file.
For example,
we want to check the angle of the end of two panels.
First, select the edit panel tool
from the 2D window tool bar.
Select the panel end point to check the angle.
Press the right mouse button and select the left and right mouse buttons.
Press the end point button
to show the angle of this point.
The shape of the panel
will change according to the angle of the end of two panels.
In this case,
you can check the angle
and modify the panel
to modify it to the shape you want.
You can also open the 2D edit panel
to display the length of the line or the angle function.
You can check all the angles of the panels.
The angle of the overlap between the lines
in the pocket
can also be displayed.
And the angle can also be changed
according to the movement of the lines.
This function can make it easy for us to check
the angle of the special position of the panel.
Next is the optimization of the seam allowance.
First, I will introduce the optimization
of the seam allowance.
Before this,
when there is a seam allowance at the corner of the panel,
after adding the seam allowance,
the seam allowance at the extension of the panel
will create a repeated seam allowance.
However, if this is the way to create it,
the seam allowance of the seam allowance
does not match the seam allowance
that actually needs to be cut,
so the sewing information may be inaccurate.
In order to improve this problem,
we will provide two options
to determine the position of the seam allowance in the seam allowance.
First, use the cut tool to select the cut.
In the attribute editor,
you can find that the cut menu of the corner cut
and the cut menu of the seam allowance
are different.
When choosing the corner cut,
a new cut position menu will appear.
You can choose to duplicate the cut
to the extension point or the center position.
In the case of this seam allowance,
when choosing the extension point,
the cut position is displayed
from the level of the cut of the panel
and the position of the vertical extension to the point.
When choosing the center position,
the cut is displayed
in the extension position of the corner as it is now.
This improvement can help us provide
more accurate panel information.
Next is another optimization related to the seam allowance.
This is another optimization related to the seam allowance.
It supports the addition of seam allowance
on the hollow inside the panel.
Before this,
the seam allowance tool can only be created
from the outline of the panel.
From the previous version,
it can be updated to identify the hollow as the outline,
so it can also create a seam allowance for the hollow.
In the 2D window,
select the seam allowance tool,
then select the hollow position
to select the position to create the seam allowance.
Then you can see that
the hollow position has been identified as the outline
and the seam allowance has been created.
Due to the possibility of creating a seam allowance
in the hollow,
the seam allowance can be displayed in the hollow.
Through the function of the improvement,
it can be completed in the CLO
in a more diversified version than before.
Next is the improvement of the 2D paper pattern.
In the previous version,
if the paper pattern created in the 2D CAD
is located at a position far away from the center,
then the position of the paper pattern
then the location will remain the original and be entered into the CLO.
Therefore, it is necessary to re-create the paper sample in the 00 position
in order to find all the paper samples in the CLO conveniently.
However, from the latest version, when downloading DXF files,
the file will be based in the 00 position and the center of the 2D window,
while maintaining all the existing rows of paper samples.
The improved DXF input function can help everyone
to improve the efficiency of work.
Next is the improvement of the code selection.
In the updated version, the object window code display has been optimized.
When opening and displaying the code in the CLO,
the color of the code line will be displayed randomly,
and in the option of the object window code,
click the button of the eye next to the color block
to display or hide the specified size of the code line.
You can also click the color block to remove the color board
to modify the color of the code line.
When creating a new code size, the color will also be generated randomly.
You can also choose the color block after the name of the size
to remove the color board to select the desired color.
In the same way, when opening and displaying the code in the CLO mode,
the color of the different size of the board will be displayed randomly.
You can also change the color of the board in the color block mode.
In this way, we can automatically create a color in the code selection,
or the specified color,
to identify the paper sample with the code line
or the paper sample in the hard disk mode.
Next is the introduction of the new hair hair function.
First, the hair hair material has been added to the compensation light,
which is the Composite Energy option.
When the hair density is higher, the light may not be able to come out between the hair lines,
causing the rendering to be darker than normal.
Opening this option can correct the lost light,
making the hair brightness closer to the real effect.
In addition, from the current version,
the CLO rendering has been added to the V-Ray support.
First, apply the hair hair material to the board.
The hair hair effect can only be checked in the rendering window,
so open the rendering in the
V-Ray mode.
Now we have the length, thickness, density,
curl, gravity, curve strength,
curve direction, and initial direction.
So now we can apply 8 hair patterns.
Now we can apply 8 hair patterns.
Next, let's take a look at the application of the new hair
on the hair.
First is the curl pattern.
First, you can add the curl pattern
to show the number of curls
and the radius of the curl.
The curl pattern is a black and white hair pattern.
In which, the black part of the stray pattern
means that there is no curl,
while the white part of the sociedad pattern
means that it has been set to the curl.
The second one is the gravity pattern
which we can see that
bisschen more on the hair further.
The gravity pattern is also black and white futting pattern.
First, on the hair,
adding a
The third is the curve intensity sticker.
It can express the curve of the hair by using the curve intensity sticker.
The curve intensity sticker is also a black-and-white sticker.
The black area of the sticker means that there is no curve.
The white area means that there is a curve.
The fourth is the curve direction sticker.
It can be used to define the curve direction of the hair.
The curve direction sticker is an RGB sticker with color.
It determines the direction of the texture according to the color of the application.
In the actual application, we can use the hair spray picture to show the different curve directions of the hair.
The last is the initial direction sticker.
It can be used to define the initial direction of the hair by adding the initial direction sticker.
That is, the root direction.
The fourth is the curve intensity sticker.
The curve direction sticker is also an RGB sticker with color.
It determines the direction of the texture according to the color of the application.
The curve intensity sticker can also be used to show the direction of the hair root.
It shows the pattern of the hair.
Since the sticker is suitable for hair plants,
now we can apply the sticker in Substance to Claw to achieve a more realistic hair production.
Next is the update about the rendering part.
From the new version, it can render 360-degree landscape images.
In addition, it can also use the rendering space created in Claw in Clawset to build its own virtual exhibition hall.
First, import the OBJ file into Claw,
then move the position to the center of the 360-degree landscape space.
When rendering, create a wall-mounted exhibition hall on all four sides.
The 360-degree landscape image will be more natural.
Then open the rendering window and click on the camera attribute tool.
You can see that the lens part of the camera attribute window has been added to the lens type option.
Click on the download icon to see two options.
The first option is the default option and the existing lens type.
The other is the full lens option, which is the new option.
Click on the second option, the full-lens lens rendering option.
You will see that the view has been changed from default value 15 to 60.
And all models, scenes and props in the 3D window are displayed on the grid surface.
This is to make it easier to place the camera and correctly render in Vray.
Next, set the image size to the recommended size in the Clawset production manual.
The finished rendering image can be added to the space button in the edit mode.
Use it as a new space for Clawset virtual exhibition.
This is the new space for Clawset virtual exhibition.
The following is about the optimization of the rendering function.
When rendering, the object sometimes has a wave-like Morven shadow problem.
In the updated version, the image filter option has been added.
Adjust it in Vray rendering to solve the Morven problem.
First, open the rendering function.
Click on the rendering property icon in the toolbar.
You can see that a image filter option has been added to the bottom of the property editor window.
The default size of the image filter is 1.5.
Open the synchronization rendering.
You can see that there is a Morven on the clothing in the rendering window.
In this way, you can see that there is a Morven on the clothing.
The image filter size value can be adjusted to 10 at most, and the smallest to 1.
The larger the value, the less Morven shadow.
Here we can adjust the value a little bit.
After adjusting the value, we need to turn on synchronization rendering to see the adjustment effect.
From the rendering effect,
when the previous value is set to 1,
the image filter will be set to 1.5.
Let's see if there is still a Morven under the previous value.
Then we directly enter a relatively large value.
After stopping rendering,
open synchronization rendering again.
You can see that the Morven phenomenon is now almost gone.
Therefore, we can use this function to improve the rendering image effect.
If you remember the first time,
the scene has a Morven at the top left.
When this happens,
the Morven is now set at the highest value.
The Strangling effect is now shown.
This window changes to less than 1.5.
The path is now black.
We can also see that the Morven has shown the same 0.5.
Now we can see that the Morven has changed in the layout.
We can also see that the Morven has changed in the layout.
The случайlos method in the query is possible.